As my husband,
남편으로서,
I want to take care of my wife's face.
나는 아내의 얼굴을 관리하고 싶습니다.
After this, I will definitely serve the double empire.
그 후에는 반드시 이중 제국을 섬길 것입니다.
May you be united.
하나가 되기를 바랍니다.
All of you!
여러분!
Take off your clothes!
옷을 벗어라!
Stop!
멈추다!
Tuan Mucun,
투안 무쿤,
today is the wedding day
오늘은 결혼식 날이야
my nephew.
내 조카.
Your actions
당신의 행동
do this
이 작업을 수행
Something happened, sir.
무슨 일이 일어났어요, 선생님.
However, our cooperation
그러나 우리의 협력
we must continue.
우리는 계속해야합니다.
Since we want to work together,
같이 일하고 싶기 때문에,
give the surface only
표면만 제공
you arrange a woman
당신은 여자를 준비
to check him in the room,
그 사람을 방에서 확인하려고,
okey?
승인?
Good.
좋은.
Take him away.
그를 데려가세요.
Jiaping.
가평.
Jiaping, how about you?
자핑 씨, 당신은 어때요?
Keep searching.
계속 검색하세요.
Chen Jiaping.
천자핑.
If you screw up again,
또 망하면,
big spoon.
큰 숟가락.
The murder at the foot of the hill.
언덕 기슭에서의 살인.
This matter?
이 문제?
I do not understand.
난 이해가 안 돼요.
How did the killer sneak in?
범인은 어떻게 몰래 들어왔나요?
Besides that,
그 외에도
why did he go to the store room?
그 사람은 왜 창고에 갔나요?
All this is Zhao 'an's doing.
이 모든 것이 Zhao'an이 하는 일입니다.
Zhao'an?
자오안?
Originally, Zhao 'an wanted Ah Kun to identify the peach on the left,
원래 조안은 아군이 왼쪽에 있는 복숭아를 알아내길 원했고,
didn't think he had caused Shanxia's death.
그가 Shanxia의 죽음을 초래했다고 생각하지 않았습니다.
There are more left twin peaches.
남은 쌍둥이 복숭아가 더 있어요.
You mean this peach?
이 복숭아 말하는 거야?
We investigate.
우리는 조사합니다.
With Zhao 'an too.
Zhao'an도 마찬가지입니다.
Investigate thoroughly.
철저하게 조사하세요.
Does he have a problem?
그에게 문제가 있나요?
The Left Cavalry is in trouble now.
좌익 기병대는 지금 곤경에 처해 있습니다.
I can't say he has problems either.
나는 그에게도 문제가 있다고 말할 수 없습니다.
Your brain is stupid.
당신의 두뇌는 바보입니다.
Now, Zhao An is in trouble.
이제 조안은 곤경에 빠졌습니다.
He can take responsibility
그는 책임을 질 수 있다
This is our chance.
이것이 우리의 기회입니다.
Why?
왜?
Hands are so cold.
손이 너무 차갑습니다.
Still shivering.
아직도 떨고 있어요.
A scary thing happened.
무서운 일이 일어났습니다.
I'm afraid.
나는 두려워한다.
Afraid of what?
무엇이 두렵 니?
Nothing to do with us.
우리와는 아무 상관이 없습니다.
Know I'm a coward.
내가 겁쟁이라는 걸 알아라.
Especially when you see a dead person.
특히 죽은 사람을 볼 때는 더욱 그렇습니다.
Definitely can't sleep well lately.
확실히 요즘 잠을 잘 못 자요.
Lao.
라오스.
You still remember,
아직도 기억하시나요?
when we were new together,
우리가 새로 만났을 때,
the late night meal you often take me to eat.
네가 자주 나한테 데려가는 야식.
Kedai Cui Hua?
케다이 추이화?
Remember.
기억하다.
You said, the wedding ceremony is today
오늘 결혼식이 있다고 했잖아
ended in a hurry.
급하게 끝났습니다.
I'm not full yet
아직 배 안찼어
and scared to death.
그리고 겁에 질려 죽는다.
I'm begging you.
부탁드립니다.
Take me out to eat again,
또 먹으러 나가서
okey?
승인?
Of.
의.
It's been more than two years
2년이 넘었어요
it's late at night we haven't eaten together, right?
늦은 밤인데 우리는 함께 식사를 하지 않았죠?
Good.
좋은.
Thank You.
감사합니다.
So sick, right?
너무 아프지 않나요?
Luckily your heart was not injured.
다행히 심장은 다치지 않으셨네요.
Guoguo.
궈궈.
Sorry.
죄송합니다.
For not protecting you.
당신을 보호하지 않아서.
The Japanese do not respect us.
일본인은 우리를 존경하지 않습니다.
Why are you still working for them?
왜 아직도 그 사람들 밑에서 일하고 있나요?
I know.
알아요.
After I get the profit,
이익을 얻은 후,
let's go, okay?
가자, 응?
Now,
지금,
I have my own plans.
나는 나만의 계획을 가지고 있습니다.
Trust me.
날 믿어.
I went to work at a trading bank.
나는 무역 은행에 일하러 갔다.
I am your friend.
나는 당신의 친구입니다.
You have to go to work in a bank.
은행에 가서 일해야 합니다.
Guoguo.
궈궈.
This is dangerous when working for the Japanese.
이것은 일본인을 위해 일할 때 위험합니다.
What are you going to do?
당신은 무엇을 할 예정입니까?
After all, what can you do with your shop?
결국, 당신은 당신의 가게에서 무엇을 할 수 있나요?
I am an accountant.
내가 회계사입니다.
After all, I can ask Luo Guanqun to agree.
결국 Luo Guanqun에게 동의하도록 요청할 수 있습니다.
But, the most important thing is that I can go to the bank.
하지만 가장 중요한 것은 은행에 갈 수 있다는 것입니다.
I can go to the bank.
은행에 갈 수 있어요.
To take care of my husband.
남편을 돌보기 위해.
Your voice is more friendly
목소리가 더 친근해요
more useful than painkillers?
진통제보다 더 유용하다?
Scream again.
다시 비명을 지르세요.
Go away.
저리 가요.
I almost died.
거의 죽을 뻔 했어.
are you kidding
농담하는 거야?
I mean it.
진심이야.
Dear.
에게.
It would be nice if there was no war.
전쟁만 안 나면 좋을 텐데.
All this will end.
이 모든 것이 끝날 것입니다.
I still don't agree
나는 아직도 동의하지 않는다
if you want to go to work
네가 일하러 가고 싶다면
You are my wife.
당신은 내 아내입니다.
You have to listen to me.
당신은 내 말을 들어야합니다.
Just today.
바로 오늘입니다.
Just today?
오늘만요?
You don't follow me?
당신은 나를 따르지 않습니까?
My wound hurts again.
상처가 또 아프네요.
Team Leader Zhao,
자오 팀장,
Shuyun.
슈윤.
It's me.
나야.
Only you don't give up on me.
오직 당신만이 나를 포기하지 않습니다.
No matter what time,
시간에 상관없이,
I will not give up on you.
나는 너를 포기하지 않을 것이다.
Shuyun,
슈윤,
why?
왜?
You are no longer useful.
당신은 더 이상 쓸모가 없습니다.
Tuan Mucun!
투안 무쿤!
Forgive me, sir.
용서해주세요.
Awak yang mengahwinkan Chen Jiaping dan Zuo Shuangtao?
Awak yang mengahwinkan Chen Jiaping dan Zuo Shuangtao?
Your plan.
당신의 계획.
Let Ah Kun go to the wedding venue,
아군을 결혼식장으로 보내주고,
to the wedding.
결혼식에.
Your bad ideas come one after another.
당신의 나쁜 생각이 차례로 나옵니다.
The hole was getting bigger.
구멍은 점점 커져만 갔다.
You are the one who caused the army down the hill
군대를 언덕 아래로 몰락하게 만든 장본인은 바로 당신입니다
take Ah Kun to the wedding!
아군을 결혼식에 데려가세요!
Ya, ya.
응, 응.
Raised by the bottom of the mountain player himself.
산 밑바닥 선수가 직접 키웠습니다.
It is not our responsibility.
그것은 우리의 책임이 아닙니다.
What? We...
무엇? 우리...
No, I...
아니, 난...
I said it wrong.
내가 잘못 말했다.
I...
나...
I have understood.
나는 이해했다.
You mean
네 말 뜻은
death of a relief player
구원투수 사망
I am also responsible for it.
나에게도 책임이 있다.
You want to tell me
당신은 나에게 말하고 싶어
how can a good player die?
좋은 선수가 어떻게 죽을 수 있나요?
to yourself?
너 자신에게?
Don't dare, can't.
감히 할 수 없습니다.
I... I don't dare and I won't do that.
난... 감히 그럴 수도 없고 그렇게 하지도 않을 거예요.
I will not and dare not.
나는 그렇게 하지 않을 것이며 감히 그렇게 하지 않을 것이다.
Diam!
디암!
Diam.
직경
Don't, Chief Mumura. Listen.
그러지 마세요, 무무라 대장. 듣다.
I am raising funds for the launch of Project Shan
저는 Project Shan 출시를 위해 자금을 모으고 있습니다.
for the launch of the Shan Plan.
Shan 계획의 시작을 위해.
You killed me Zhao 'an?
당신이 나를 죽였나요? 자오안?
Its okay.
괜찮아요.
My life is worthless.
내 인생은 가치가 없습니다.
However, funds were not enough.
그러나 자금이 충분하지 않았습니다.
It will slow down the Shan Project process.
Shan 프로젝트 프로세스가 느려질 것입니다.
It will delay the success of the empire.
그것은 제국의 성공을 지연시킬 것입니다.
You want to threaten me?
나를 위협하고 싶나요?
I'm afraid.
나는 두려워한다.
I don't dare and I won't do that.
나는 감히 그럴 수도 없고 그렇게 하지도 않을 것이다.
Diam!
디암!
Diam.
직경
Zhao 'an.
자오안.
Actually, your life is gone.
사실, 당신의 인생은 사라졌습니다.
No more.
더 이상은 없어.
It's just kept here temporarily.
일시적으로 여기에 보관되어 있을 뿐입니다.
Fine.
괜찮은.
If this mission fails again,
만약 이번 미션이 또 실패한다면,
I will waste your life
나는 당신의 인생을 낭비할 것입니다
like throwing out trash.
쓰레기 버리는 것처럼.
Throw it away!
멀리 던져!
In the shit hole.
똥구멍에.
Toilet?
화장실?
don't kill me
나를 죽이지 마세요
please
제발
Tuan Mucun.
투안 무쿤.
Thank You.
감사합니다.
Mr Mumura.
무무라 씨.
Left, two pics.
왼쪽, 두 장의 사진.
Has Your Honor not checked yet?
재판장님 아직 확인 안하셨나요?
Ah Kun's counter indeed
아쿤의 카운터는 과연
engraved with left peach.
왼쪽 복숭아가 새겨져 있습니다.
I think that's definitely not a coincidence.
나는 그것이 결코 우연이 아니라고 생각한다.
Trust me.
날 믿어.
Or is there another possibility?
아니면 또 다른 가능성이 있나요?
This is a trap designed by Ah Kun and the Left Cavalry.
이것은 아군과 좌기병이 설계한 함정이다.
To bring the dancers into the room.
댄서들을 방으로 데려오려고요.
Trust me.
날 믿어.
Don't waste your time.
시간을 낭비하지 마십시오.
Peach on the left.
왼쪽이 복숭아.
You should know
당신은 알고 있어야
you should know clearly
분명히 알아야 해
What is the most important task?
가장 중요한 업무는 무엇인가요?
Of.
의.
I will try my best
난 내 최선을 다할 것입니다
to find the two consultants.
두 명의 컨설턴트를 찾기 위해.
Don't worry.
괜찮아요.
Since they are both married,
둘 다 결혼한 상태이기 때문에
us
우리를
water to keep fish.
물고기를 키우는 물.
Look at the situation later.
나중에 상황을 보세요.
How about your wound?
상처는 어때요?
It's impossible to die.
죽는 것은 불가능합니다.
Oh yes.
바로 이거 야.
Is the picture I took
내가 찍은 사진인가
have you washed it?
씻어봤어?
Captured documents are very valuable.
캡처된 문서는 매우 귀중합니다.
But,
하지만,
dokumen Zhao 'an ini
문서 자오안이니
when compared to the Shan Plan,
Shan 계획과 비교했을 때,
even though I don't care.
내가 상관하지 않더라도.
Even so,
비록 그렇다 하더라도,
It was also a huge success.
또한 큰 성공을 거두었습니다.
Before this, we only had
그 전에는 우리만 있었어요.
Sushan's previous program.
수샨의 이전 프로그램.
However, I couldn't get any further information.
그러나 더 이상의 정보는 얻을 수 없었습니다.
I have informed my superiors.
나는 상사에게 알렸다.
Your next assignment
다음 과제
is directly investigating the Shan Program.
Shan 프로그램을 직접 조사하고 있습니다.
I understand.
이해합니다.
Oh yes.
바로 이거 야.
Sebelum ini, Luo Guanqun dan Zhao An
Sebelum ini, Luo Guanqun dan Zhao An
pernah mengesyaki Zuo Shuangtao
페르나 멘게샤키 주오 솽타오
the killer in the foothill warrior murder.
산기슭 전사 살인의 살인자.
But I didn't take it seriously before now.
하지만 지금까지는 심각하게 받아들이지 않았습니다.
I think that's just a coincidence.
나는 그것이 단지 우연이라고 생각한다.
However, in the wedding ceremony,
그러나 결혼식에서는
The Left Cavalry's actions were so strange.
좌익기병대의 행동은 참으로 이상했다.
I was thinking,
나는 생각하고 있었다,
is he also a member of the Anti-Japanese Organization?
그 사람도 반일단체 소속인가?
You are right.
당신 말이 맞아요.
Now, he wants to
이제 그는 원한다
to work in the store.
가게에서 일하려고.
Although I do not agree,
비록 동의하지는 않지만,
based on his character,
그 사람의 성격에 따라,
I can't stop it.
나는 그것을 멈출 수 없다.
I think,
제 생각에는,
(Will he be the same as me)
(그 사람도 나와 같을까)
(There are also hidden tasks.)
(숨겨진 작업도 있습니다.)
I'll report it
신고할게요
I will report to the superiors as soon as possible
최대한 빨리 상부에 보고하겠습니다.
to conduct a more detailed investigation.
좀 더 자세한 조사를 하기 위해.
However, you are husband and wife now.
그러나 당신은 이제 남편과 아내입니다.
No matter what his true identity is,
그의 진짜 정체가 무엇이든 간에,
the first thing you need to do is
당신이 가장 먼저 해야 할 일은
is to protect the security of one's own identity.
자신의 신원을 안전하게 보호하는 것입니다.
Watch his next move.
그의 다음 행보를 지켜보세요.
Don't compromise his mission.
그의 임무를 타협하지 마십시오.
The situation is getting more complicated.
상황은 더욱 복잡해지고 있습니다.
Difficult to understand.
이해하기 어렵다.
Luo Guanqun, I told you.
Luo Guanqun, 내가 말했잖아요.
If the pic is less than half a feather from the left,
사진이 왼쪽에서 깃털의 절반 미만인 경우,
I will never let you go!
나는 결코 당신을 놓아주지 않을 것입니다!
Why are you so
넌 왜 그렇게
why is it so big?
왜 그렇게 큰가요?
look at you
당신을 보면
You are injured, not healed yet.
당신은 부상을 입었지만 아직 치유되지 않았습니다.
Rest first before coming to work.
출근 전 먼저 휴식을 취하세요.
Isn't it because of you?
너 때문은 아니지?
How can you agree with Zuo Shuangtao?
Zuo Shuangtao의 의견에 어떻게 동의할 수 있나요?
Coming to work here?
여기 일하러 오시나요?
Boss Yu came to see me.
유 사장이 나를 만나러 왔다.
I must take care of his face.
나는 그의 얼굴을 돌보아야 한다.
After all,
결국,
you two go find me now.
너희 둘은 지금 나를 찾으러 가거라.
That's right!
좋아요!
You don't see
당신은 볼 수 없습니다
This is our great opportunity.
이것은 우리의 좋은 기회입니다.
Where is she?
그녀는 어디 있습니까?
Zhao 'an has lost now.
Zhao'an은 이제 패배했습니다.
We must take this opportunity to attack them.
우리는 이 기회를 빌어 그들을 공격해야 합니다.
Boss Yu has already talked to me.
유 사장은 이미 나에게 말을 걸었다.
He has a number of...
그는 여러 가지를 가지고 있습니다 ...
There are essential seed oils in the market.
시중에는 필수 종자유가 있습니다.
For me to make sales.
내가 판매를 하기 위해서요.
We keep it for three months.
우리는 그것을 3개월 동안 보관합니다.
Then, spread the rumor.
그런 다음 소문을 퍼뜨립니다.
Rapeseed oil has risen suddenly.
유채기름이 갑자기 올랐네요.
Then it was sold...
그러다가 팔렸는데...
The money has come in.
돈이 들어왔습니다.
If not for the Left Cavalry,
좌익 기병대가 아니라면,
can Boss Yu have a chat with me?
유 상사가 나랑 얘기 좀 할 수 있을까?
You can't even allow it
당신은 그것을 허용할 수 없습니다
Zuo Shuangtao came to work here?
Zuo Shuangtao가 여기에서 일하러 왔나요?
He came to give a good image.
좋은 이미지를 주기 위해 왔다.
Are you afraid he is in danger?
그 사람이 위험에 처한 게 두렵나요?
I'm more scared than you.
나는 당신보다 더 무서워요.
I do not care.
난 상관 없어.
You must guarantee.
보장해야 합니다.
That Left Guard
그 왼쪽 경비병
will not be exposed to hazardous work.
위험한 작업에 노출되지 않습니다.
I guarantee.
나는 보장한다.
I have ten thousand guaranteed.
만개 보장합니다.
Mari.
마리.
Sit down first.
먼저 앉으세요.
Zhao 'an disokong oleh Mucun.
Zhao 'an disokong oleh Mucun.
Who are you?
누구세요?
Not enough to eat.
먹기에 충분하지 않습니다.
Who are you to hurt Zhao 'an?
Zhao 'an을 다치게 하는 당신은 누구입니까?
What does Mucun want?
무쿤은 무엇을 원하는가?
Business and money.
사업과 돈.
Business and money are with us.
사업과 돈은 우리와 함께 있습니다.
Mucun will join the trend.
무쿤도 그 트렌드에 동참하겠습니다.
Good.
좋은.
Everything you said is true.
당신이 말한 모든 것은 사실입니다.
Hope you
당신이 그러기를 바란다
do not forget me
저를 잊지 마세요
do not forget me.
저를 잊지 마세요.
Don't worry.
괜찮아요.
Forget who?
누구를 잊어버리셨나요?
I will never forget you either.
나도 당신을 결코 잊지 않을 것입니다.
Oh yes.
바로 이거 야.
Do you still remember?
아직도 기억하시나요?
During your wedding ceremony,
결혼식 도중,
Why did Zhao 'an call Ah Kun there?
자오안은 왜 거기로 아쿤을 불렀나요?
Let go of my hand!
내 손을 놔라!
I do not suspect the Left Cavalry,
나는 좌익기병을 의심하지 않는다.
if not, can I allow him to come to work here?
그렇지 않다면 그가 여기에서 일하도록 허락해도 될까요?
Why are you asking this question?
왜 이런 질문을 하시나요?
Mari.
마리.
Sit down,
앉아,
Your behavior is really bad.
당신의 행동은 정말 나쁩니다.
Zhao 'an has fallen into the well.
조안이 우물에 빠졌어요.
Still not breathing.
아직도 숨을 쉬지 않습니다.
We want to throw stones inside.
우리는 안에 돌을 던지고 싶습니다.
What stone?
무슨 돌?
You should be able to find Zhao 'an's evidence
자오안의 증거를 찾을 수 있을 거예요
you need to find evidence that Zhao 'an is still guilty.
자오안이 여전히 유죄라는 증거를 찾아야 합니다.
When you say that,
당신이 그렇게 말할 때,
(I remembered something else strange.)
(또 이상한 일이 생각났어요.)
On my wedding day,
내 결혼식 날,
feng Qi went first?
Feng Qi가 먼저 갔나요?
Before the wedding,
결혼식 전,
Zhao 'an told Feng Seven something.
Zhao'an은 Feng Seven에게 뭔가를 말했습니다.
Feng seven left in a hurry.
펑세븐은 서둘러 떠났다.
Probably nothing to do with
아마 아무 관련도 없을 거야
with the hero's murder at the foot of the mountain,
산기슭에서 영웅의 살해와 함께
but always make others remember.
하지만 항상 다른 사람들이 기억하게 해주세요.
Then, go scheme Feng Qi.
그런 다음 Feng Qi 계획을 세우십시오.
No, how do I investigate?
아니, 어떻게 조사하나요?
I investigated without evidence.
증거도 없이 조사했어요.
What if something happens to him?
그에게 무슨 일이 생기면 어쩌지?
Actually,
실제로,
remind you
당신을 생각 나게
Doesn't it make you suspicious?
의심스럽지 않나요?
If there is any doubt, can you not investigate?
조금이라도 의심되면 조사하면 안되나요?
Of course no problem.
물론 문제 없습니다.
Isn't it better to investigate?
조사해 보는 게 낫지 않을까요?
You don't know this theory.
당신은 이 이론을 모른다.
That's right.
좋아요.
Team leader.
팀 리더.
I met the two Japanese people
일본인 두명을 만났어요
I met the two Japanese people.
일본인 두 명을 만났습니다.
But when followed to Mingzhe University,
하지만 Mingzhe University에 진학했을 때,
after that disappear.
그 후에는 사라집니다.
I've been looking here for a day.
나는 하루 동안 여기를 찾고 있었다.
Personal hair is not visible.
개인 머리카락은 보이지 않습니다.
Wait for me there.
거기서 기다리세요.
I will come soon.
곧 올게요.
Good.
좋은.
Why so many people
왜 그렇게 많은 사람들이
why are so many people here today?
오늘 여기 왜 이렇게 사람이 많아?
Dysentery has been going on for the past two days.
지난 이틀 동안 이질이 계속되었습니다.
Many Japanese soldiers and their family members contracted the disease.
많은 일본 군인과 그 가족이 이 질병에 걸렸습니다.
The hospital was full of people.
병원은 사람들로 가득 차 있었다.
I'm sure,
확실해,
they are both in the Army General Hospital.
둘 다 육군 종합병원에 있어요.
I will act tomorrow morning.
내일 아침에 행동하겠습니다.
You go to Army General Hospital to kill people?
사람을 죽이려고 육군종합병원에 간다고?
You don't want to die?
죽고 싶지 않아?
You have forgotten, Mr. Mumura once said,
당신은 잊어버렸습니다. 무무라 씨는 이렇게 말했습니다.
this matter must be kept confidential.
이 문제는 비밀로 유지되어야 합니다.
And don't involve us.
그리고 우리를 개입시키지 마세요.
What should we do?
우리는 무엇을 해야 합니까?
Find the killer
살인자를 찾아라
entered the hospital disguised as a cleaner.
청소부로 변장하여 병원에 들어갔다.
After the incident,
사건 이후,
remove badness let it end.
나쁜 것을 제거하고 끝내십시오.
Team leader.
팀 리더.
You have thought carefully.
곰곰히 생각해보셨네요.
I do now.
지금 할게.
I know the man in the gray robe.
나는 회색 옷을 입은 남자를 안다.
He is a killer.
그는 살인자입니다.
He was nicknamed Handalan.
그는 Handalan이라는 별명을 얻었습니다.
There are several lives in my hands.
내 손에는 여러 생명이 있습니다.
Hiding in a French concession for several years.
몇 년 동안 프랑스 조계지에 숨어 있었습니다.
But, the strange thing is,
그런데 이상한 점은,
zhao 'an wants to kill people.
자오안은 사람을 죽이고 싶어한다.
Why are his men not moving?
그의 부하들은 왜 움직이지 않는 걸까요?
Instead, find another killer.
대신 다른 살인자를 찾아보세요.
After following this ghost,
이 유령을 따라간 후,
we'll know who Zhao'an's target is.
우리는 Zhao'an의 목표가 누구인지 알게 될 것입니다.
Do you want me to go with you?
내가 당신과 함께 갈까요?
Let it be.
순리에 맡기다.
He has long worked in the French concession.
그는 오랫동안 프랑스 조계지에서 일해 왔습니다.
Maybe I've met you.
어쩌면 내가 당신을 만났을 수도 있습니다.
I went alone.
나는 혼자 갔다.
Be careful.
조심하세요.
Is it time to negotiate?
이제 협상할 시간인가?
Of.
의.
Don't worry.
괜찮아요.
I have told them to prepare.
나는 그들에게 준비하라고 말했습니다.
However, I hope our negotiations this time
하지만 이번에는 협상이 이루어지기를 바랍니다.
can run smoothly and successfully
원활하고 성공적으로 진행될 수 있습니다
smoothly and successfully
원활하고 성공적으로
and captured China peacefully.
평화롭게 중국을 점령했습니다.
Of.
의.
Do not worry.
걱정 하지마.
Both of you
너희 둘 다
go to wards 1-3 on the ground floor.
1층 1~3병동으로 가세요.
Why?
왜?
Ward on the second floor...
2층 병실..
Has been used as an isolation ward.
격리 병동으로 사용되었습니다.
Pack things.
물건을 포장하세요.
There is medicine spilled in this medicine room.
이 약실에 약이 흘렀습니다.
Please go clean up.
가서 청소하세요.
Okay.
좋아요.
Good!
좋은!
I'm a killer!
나는 살인자입니다!
Someone is spending money to kill you.
누군가가 당신을 죽이려고 돈을 쓰고 있습니다.
There are also people who spend money to get information
정보를 얻기 위해 돈을 쓰는 사람들도 있습니다
which one is your policy?
당신의 정책은 어느 것입니까?
I guess,
아마도,
but I need more people to get information.
하지만 정보를 얻으려면 더 많은 사람이 필요해요.
So, if you tell me...
그러니까, 나한테 말하면...
The information I want,
내가 원하는 정보는,
I will let you both go.
너희 둘 다 보내주겠다.
My patience has its limits.
내 인내심에는 한계가 있습니다.
How do we deal with it?
우리는 그것을 어떻게 처리합니까?
Can't say
말할 수 없다
he will kill us.
그는 우리를 죽일 것입니다.
Tell him false information.
그에게 거짓 정보를 말하십시오.
How did he find us?
그 사람이 우리를 어떻게 찾았나요?
Is to communicate closely
긴밀하게 소통하는 것입니다
secret leak of peace talks?
평화회담 비밀 유출?
Apparently, I can only profit less.
분명히 나는 ​​이익을 덜 얻을 수 있습니다.
Don't.
하지 않다.
Who?
WHO?
Why did Zhao 'an send an assassin
조안은 왜 암살자를 보냈나
kill the two Japanese?
일본인 두 명을 죽여?
Who are these two Japanese people?
이 두 일본인은 누구입니까?
Are they pro-China or anti-war?
그들은 친중국인가, 아니면 반전인가?
Unfortunately, I don't understand Japanese
불행하게도 나는 일본어를 모른다.
some Japanese words.
일본어 단어 몇개.
Left, two pics.
왼쪽, 두 장의 사진.
Act smart.
현명하게 행동하세요.
Defying military orders,
군사명령을 거부하고,
not only remove secret letters that are difficult to find...
찾기 힘든 비밀편지를 제거할 뿐만 아니라...
Hard to get,
구하기 힘든,
in fact, dare to continue hiding.
사실 감히 계속 숨어 있습니다.
Is it your superiors?
당신의 상사입니까?
or no organization?
아니면 조직이 없나요?
I think definitely taken by
내 생각엔 확실히 데려간 것 같아
taken by people in the store.
매장에 있는 사람들이 찍은 것.
So, I kept lurking,
그래서 계속 숨어 있었는데,
I will definitely be able to find it again.
꼭 다시 찾을 수 있을 거예요.
You feel everything
당신은 모든 것을 느낍니다
It's easy to hide, isn't it?
숨기는 게 참 쉽죠?
Luo Guanqun.
루오 관쿤.
Tell me to work in a commercial bank in three days.
3일 후에 상업 은행에서 일하라고 말해 주세요.
Add to that my brother's father's relationship with Yu Shanren,
여기에 내 형의 아버지와 Yu Shanren의 관계도 추가됩니다.
I can definitely succeed.
나는 반드시 성공할 수 있다.
Don't think I don't know.
내가 모른다고 생각하지 마세요.
If you continue to live in Shanghai,
상하이에 계속 거주한다면,
don't you want to stay with Chen Jiaping?
Chen Jiaping과 함께 있고 싶지 않습니까?
I do not have.
난 없어.
Don't quibble.
불평하지 마십시오.
I disobeyed orders.
나는 명령에 불복종했습니다.
Please give me punishment.
저에게 처벌을 주십시오.
Do not miss to punish you,
당신을 처벌하는 것을 놓치지 마세요,
I can execute the death penalty for you.
나는 당신을 위해 사형을 집행할 수 있습니다.
I won't regret it.
나는 그것을 후회하지 않을 것이다.
You are stubborn.
너는 고집이 세다.
I let you stay in Shanghai.
나는 당신을 상하이에 머물게 했습니다.
What is your mission?
당신의 임무는 무엇입니까?
he worked at a merchant bank
그는 상업은행에서 일했어요
to keep looking for information.
계속해서 정보를 찾으려고요.
Of.
의.
The truth will emerge after acting.
진실은 행동한 뒤에 드러날 것이다.
Watch movie?
영화를보고?
Candlelight dinner.
촛불 저녁 식사.
All your behavior
당신의 모든 행동
like a newly married couple.
마치 신혼부부처럼.
But the most important thing is
하지만 가장 중요한 것은
don't let Chen Jiaping doubt you.
Chen Jiaping이 당신을 의심하게 두지 마십시오.
Of.
의.
I will get the job done!
나는 일을 끝낼 것이다!
We can no longer disobey orders.
우리는 더 이상 명령을 거역할 수 없습니다.
It's your turn now.
이제 당신 차례입니다.
Find me for what?
무엇 때문에 나를 찾아?
Before Miss Hanlu
미스한루 전
have collaborated with
와 협력했습니다
with Manchuria, right?
만주랑 맞죠?
Of.
의.
If so, it seems,
그렇다면 그럴 것 같습니다.
you too
너도
Miss Hanlu is very good at Japanese, right?
한루 선생님은 일본어를 아주 잘하시죠?
I don't dare to say that I am completely proficient.
나는 감히 내가 완전히 능숙하다고 말할 수 없습니다.
There is no problem in normal communication.
정상적인 의사소통에는 문제가 없습니다.
Actually this is how it is.
실제로는 이렇습니다.
I want to ask Miss Han Lu to help me
한루 선생님께 도와달라고 부탁하고 싶어요
translate some Japanese words to me.
나에게 일본어 단어 몇 개를 번역해 주세요.
However, it is not a complete sentence.
그러나 완전한 문장은 아닙니다.
Just a few paragraphs.
몇 단락만요.
After all, my pronunciation might not be good enough.
결국 내 발음이 부족할 수도 있다.
Speak up.
발언.
I tried.
나는 노력했다.
Thank You.
감사합니다.
I copied it on paper.
종이에 복사했어요.
And mention the peace talks with the Chongqing government.
그리고 충칭 정부와의 평화 회담에 대해서도 언급하세요.
Another secret leak.
또 다른 비밀 유출.
Chongqing government peace talks.
충칭 정부 평화 회담.
Thank You.
감사합니다.
Besides that,
그 외에도
don't tell anyone.
아무에게도 말하지 마세요.
Yes?
예?
That's right.
좋아요.
Talk to smart people
똑똑한 사람들과 대화하세요
This is so exciting.
정말 흥미롭습니다.
Miss Han Lu,
한루 선생님,
you have to keep a secret for me again.
나한테 또 비밀을 지켜줘야 해.
I already know
나는 이미 알고 있다
men have many secrets.
남자들은 비밀이 많아요.
Keep a secret
비밀을 유지하세요
It has to keep a lot of secrets.
많은 비밀을 지켜야 합니다.
Miss Lu must be
미스 루는 틀림없어요
also a person who has many secrets, right?
비밀도 많은 사람이잖아요?
Maybe someday,
언젠가는,
I will tell you my secret.
내 비밀을 말해주지.
Team leader, team leader.
팀장, 팀장.
Have you run?
달려봤어?
where have you gone
어디 갔다
I've been looking for a long time near the hospital, but I can't find it.
병원 근처를 오랫동안 찾아봤는데 못찾겠어요.
Feng Qi.
펭 치.
Why do you use two knives?
왜 칼을 두 개 사용합니까?
There is no perfect solution.
완벽한 해결책은 없습니다.
Worse.
더 나쁜.
Not.
아니다.
If not suddenly there is a fake doctor,
갑자기 가짜 의사가 나오지 않는다면,
this operation will succeed.
이 작업은 성공할 것입니다.
Fake doctor!
가짜 의사!
Did you see that?
그거 봤어?
He wore a face covering.
그는 얼굴 가리개를 착용했습니다.
But you can't see his face clearly.
하지만 그의 얼굴은 명확하게 볼 수 없습니다.
Why did you take me to see the movie?
왜 나를 영화보러 데려갔나요?
After marriage, can't watch movies?
결혼하고 나면 영화를 볼 수 없나요?
Yes.
예.
But why did you invite me to see Hanlu's movie?
그런데 왜 한루의 영화를 보자고 나를 초대한 걸까요?
Didn't think he was already acting.
그가 이미 연기를 하고 있다고는 생각하지 못했습니다.
I want to know, I will definitely not buy!
나는 알고 싶습니다. 나는 절대 사지 않을 것입니다!
Go away!
저리 가요!
Are you really mad?
정말 화가 났나요?
I went to the toilet.
나는 화장실에 갔다.
Pic two from left.
왼쪽에서 두 번째 사진.
What are you doing?
뭐하세요?
I should ask you.
물어봐야겠어요.
What are you doing here?
여기서 뭐하는거야?
Why pretend to be a peddler?
왜 행상인인 척합니까?
Why don't you leave Shanghai?
상하이를 떠나는 게 어때요?
I...
나...
Must act properly.
제대로 행동해야 합니다.
Watch movie?
영화를보고?
Candlelight dinner.
촛불 저녁 식사.
All your behavior
당신의 모든 행동
like a newly married couple.
마치 신혼부부처럼.
Why do you want to kill Chen Jiaping?
왜 Chen Jiaping을 죽이고 싶습니까?
This is an order.
이것은 명령입니다.
He still has a function.
그는 여전히 기능을 가지고 있습니다.
He can't die.
그는 죽을 수 없습니다.
I can't submit my assignment.
과제를 제출할 수 없습니다.
Apparently, let me watch a movie with Chen Jiaping
아무래도 Chen Jiaping과 함께 영화를 보자
This is a conspiracy.
이것은 음모입니다.
He should choose legal concessions.
그는 법적 양보를 선택해야 합니다.
Why?
왜?
Easy to escape after success.
성공 후 탈출하기 쉽습니다.
Captain Liu told me to do this.
Liu 선장은 나에게 이렇게 하라고 말했습니다.
I think there must be a reason.
이유가 있을 것 같아요.
Go back.
돌아가세요.
I will explain to Captain Liu.
류 선장에게 설명하겠습니다.
I promise I won't bother him, okay?
그 사람을 괴롭히지 않겠다고 약속해요, 알았죠?
Look,
바라보다,
before this
이 전에
managed to kill the mountain foot warrior.
산발 전사를 죽이는 데 성공했습니다.
You trust me,
당신은 나를 신뢰합니다
right?
오른쪽?
Of.
의.
Lu's most exciting plan had just passed.
Lu의 가장 흥미로운 계획이 막 통과되었습니다.
Look at it.
보세요.
I eat kuaci.
나는 쿠아치를 먹습니다.
Look at your cold dew.
당신의 차가운 이슬을 보세요.
Very well acted.
아주 잘 행동했습니다.
Since you're shopping, I'm watching a movie,
네가 쇼핑 중이니까 나는 영화를 보고 있어
what do you say I buy you dinner?
내가 저녁 사준다고?
do you want to eat
먹을 래
Follow your words.
당신의 말을 따르십시오.
Follow me.
나를 따르라.
Jiaping.
가평.
How much Hanlu.
한루 얼마죠?
Can you sign for me?
서명해 주실 수 있나요?
Good.
좋은.
That's right.
좋아요.
Celebrities are different.
연예인은 다릅니다.
Thank You.
감사합니다.
Hello, Jiaping.
안녕하세요, 자핑님.
Do not rush.
서두르지 마.
Don't be impulsive.
충동적이지 마십시오.
Friend.
친구.
Do not act recklessly.
무모하게 행동하지 마십시오.
What do you want to know?
무엇을 알고 싶나요?
what do you want,
당신은 무엇을 원합니까?
can just say
그냥 말할 수 있어요
Do not act recklessly.
무모하게 행동하지 마십시오.
Put the gun down.
총을 내려놓으세요.
Don't come here.
여기 오지 마세요.
Otherwise, I'll shoot you!
그렇지 않으면 내가 당신을 쏠 것입니다!
According to the words of the two pics,
두 사진의 말에 따르면,
Chen Jiaping was also there at that time.
당시 천자핑(Chen Jiaping)도 거기에 있었다.
A difficult letter was in his hands.
그의 손에는 어려운 편지가 들려 있었습니다.
Since it cannot be taken back,
반품이 불가능하므로,
no possibility to leak.
누출 가능성 없음.
You must remember.
당신은 기억해야합니다.
If Chen Jiaping lives one more day,
Chen Jiaping이 하루만 더 산다면,
Another day of more danger for Double Peach left.
Double Peach에게는 또 다른 위험이 따르는 날이 남았습니다.
For the sake of the left twin pic,
왼쪽 쌍둥이 사진을 위해서,
I will definitely complete this task!
나는 이 임무를 반드시 완수할 것이다!
Do not see.
보지 마세요.
Don't look again.
다시는 보지 마세요.
Take him away.
그를 데려가세요.
you nothing?
너 아무것도 아니야?
I was surprised.
놀랐습니다.
Jiaping.
가평.
are you good
당신은 좋은가요?
How Lu.
어떻게 루.
You're welcome.
천만에요.
Thank You.
감사합니다.
Remind me
알림
Who is he?
그는 누구입니까?
Why do you want to kill me?
왜 나를 죽이고 싶나요?
I don't know either.
나도 모른다.
Anti-japanese, right?
반일(反日) 맞죠?
Cheng Zi.
쳉지.
You manage the shooting this time.
이번에는 촬영을 관리해 보세요.
Cannot be recorded in the file.
파일에 녹음할 수 없습니다.
And cannot be known by journalists.
그리고 언론인이 알 수 없습니다.
Besides that,
그 외에도
the body needs to be buried in a mass.
시체는 덩어리로 묻혀야합니다.
All right. Do not worry.
괜찮은. 걱정 하지마.
How much Hanlu.
한루 얼마죠?
why are you here
당신은 왜 여기에 있습니까?
Every time my film is shown,
내 영화가 상영될 때마다
will sit in the middle of the audience
청중 가운데 앉을 것이다
watch with them.
그들과 함께 지켜보세요.
Because, I want to know their reaction.
왜냐하면 나는 그들의 반응을 알고 싶기 때문이다.
Oh yes.
바로 이거 야.
Guoguo.
궈궈.
Mari.
마리.
I forgot to introduce you.
소개하는 걸 깜빡했어요.
This is my wife, Zuo Shuangtao.
이 사람은 내 아내 Zuo Shuangtao입니다.
Helo.
헬리콥터.
Guoguo.
궈궈.
Okay.
좋아요.
Do you know him too?
당신도 그 사람을 아시나요?
Must know.
알아야 해.
China-Japan Goodwill Ambassador.
한·일 친선대사.
Famous artist Han Lu.
유명 예술가 한루.
Actually, my profile is in many newspapers
사실 제 프로필이 여러 신문에 나왔어요
not exactly.
정확히.
I think it's quite right.
제 생각엔 꽤 맞는 것 같아요.
Jiaping.
가평.
Didn't you say he was a fan?
그 사람 팬이라고 하지 않았나요?
I didn't think he was still a close friend.
아직은 친한 친구가 아닌 것 같았어요.
I have only ever met Miss Han Lu.
나는 한루 선생님을 만난 적이 없어요.
You chat. I go first.
당신은 채팅합니다. 내가 먼저 간다.
I will go with you.
나는 당신과 함께 갈 것입니다.
Don't come with me.
나와 함께 가지 마세요.
I have my own business.
나는 내 사업이 있습니다.
Jiaping.
가평.
Did I misunderstand him?
내가 그를 오해한 걸까?
No.
아니요.
You go back first.
먼저 돌아가세요.
I will explain to Captain Liu.
류 선장에게 설명하겠습니다.
I promise I won't trouble him.
그 사람을 괴롭히지 않겠다고 약속해요.
Good?
좋은?
Ah Kun.
아쿤.
Forgive me.
용서 해줘.
Why don't you eat peaches for breakfast?
아침에 복숭아를 먹는 게 어때요?
We had a falling out recently.
우리는 최근에 탈락했습니다.
We eat separately.
우리는 따로 먹습니다.
Their relationship became strained after only a few days of marriage.
결혼한 지 불과 며칠 만에 그들의 관계는 긴장되었습니다.
Lao Lu.
라오 루.
Nothing. Sulking, arguing.
아무것도 아님. 찡그린 채, 말다툼을 합니다.
Isn't this more like a couple?
이건 좀 더 커플같지 않나요?
That's right too.
그것도 맞습니다.
Lately, the Shan Plan has shown no progress.
최근 Shan 계획은 진전을 보이지 않았습니다.
But got an unexpected profit.
그런데 뜻밖의 수익을 얻었습니다.
What?
무엇?
Did you hear that
그거 들었어?
the Chongqing government and the Japanese government
충칭 정부와 일본 정부
with the Japanese government.
일본정부와.
Peace talks?
평화 회담?
A year ago,
1년 전,
chiang kai-shek once signaled...
장개석이 한때 신호를 보냈는데...
Du Shishan, the person in charge of the Hong Kong office
Du Shishan 홍콩 지사 책임자
peace negotiations with Japan
일본과의 평화협상
also negotiated a pro-Japanese anti-communist policy.
친일·반공 정책도 협상했다.
However, Japan decided to support Wang Jingwei.
그러나 일본은 왕징웨이를 지지하기로 결정했다.
The peace talks are finally over.
드디어 평화회담이 끝났습니다.
Peace talks will resume now.
이제 평화회담이 재개될 것입니다.
It seems there is still a trick on my side.
아직 내 편에 트릭이 있는 것 같군요.
I have understood.
나는 이해했다.
I will investigate the truth as soon as possible.
최대한 빨리 진실을 조사하겠습니다.
There is one more thing.
한 가지가 더 있습니다.
I think peaches are left growing
복숭아가 계속 자라는 것 같아요
has become increasingly suspicious recently.
최근에는 점점 더 의심스러워지고 있습니다.
Before Ah Kun died,
아군이 죽기 전,
before he died.
그가 죽기 전에.
I suspect they know each other.
나는 그들이 서로를 알고 있다고 의심합니다.
Then, I remembered various doubts in the wedding ceremony.
그러다 보니 결혼식에서 있었던 여러 가지 의문점이 떠올랐다.
They sure are a bunch
확실히 무리야
or they were members of anti-Japanese organizations.
아니면 반일단체 회원이던가.
But why does Ah Kun want to kill you?
그런데 아군은 왜 당신을 죽이려고 하는 걸까요?
Take the pic from the left.
왼쪽부터 사진을 찍으세요.
And insisted on working in a trading bank.
그리고 무역 은행에서 일할 것을 고집했습니다.
Maybe he also wants to sneak into the store?
어쩌면 그도 가게에 몰래 들어가고 싶어할까요?
However, my existence
그러나 나의 존재는
is the biggest threat to him.
그에게 가장 큰 위협이다.
Left Cavalry, Peach wants to kill you.
왼쪽 기병대, 피치가 당신을 죽이고 싶어합니다.